Please say something
danger detection signal
Yudoah
Those words cannot be undone.
We're not friends anymore
Yudoah
Godred
No, I have to go home and rest.
Why do I like this better?
I can still see your face
stop looking
Ah
The night air is nice too
I wish I could just eat some ice cream
Are you saying that now?
You seem more worried about me than me.
you are really fine
You'll be fine if you eat ice cream
I think so
Then and now
It's still the same
I guess I'm a player now
I can't live any longer
Hey
I'm the one who couldn't do it, so why are you crying?
Because you don't come
child
The kid said he was okay.
It's okay
Yeah
Well, there are good things about getting hurt.
Don't get hurt
How worried were you?
Don't laugh and answer
now
It's okay
you then
no more
When you say you can't live a small life
My heart was pounding
You really liked it
What is it
This is what I really like
you didn't know
What do I not know?
Yudoah knows everything about me
The only thing I don't know
I do judo painting
I've been in unrequited love for 10 years
You don't need to know
Ugh
I'm going to tell you now
Oh, I told you not to touch my head.
I really like it
Lee Do-won
much more than you think
No, I mean
Just stick next to me like now
stay
what are you
You say that so casually?
Oh no, I’m really nervous right now.
each other's heart
The day when only sound rang out
The protagonist of the first kiss
It became my first love
I'm a little better now
No, I'm so defenseless.
No, then it's my room.
help me
uh
Just take off your clothes
arm
thank you
I have to go
I didn't shower to go to sleep.
Isn’t it then?
Oh what
once or twice
It's not like we caught it together or anything.
Is it the same as then?
Going
Go to sleep
Then I'll sleep on the floor
you're not in bed
from the side
tea
no
Why is it so hot?
ten
No, it's just hot
It's not
I have a fever
I remember
When I got really bad flu
you took care of me
Of course I remember
You didn't look like you back then
Hey
then
you don't have me
You went to the hospital early in the morning, right?
I left even when you were drunk.
thank you
Oh this
This really got people excited.
Dohwasal uh
you started it
Why are you reporting this voluntarily?
How many days of records were leaked?
Saundle Reinforcements
Lee Do-hwa's reinstatement to company
We have everything ready, even the petition.
I'll give it to you one day
why
I can't see it
Ah
I can't see because I'm shaking
Child, when you were nineteen and now
Let’s see if it’s the same.
Going
Yeah
one
two
three
It's okay
Yeah
Ah ah ah
Well, there are many other places too.
The opportunity will come again
I guess so
Then who are you?
Taekyung, you are my recognized boyfriend
No haha
Yes, yes, yes, alone, alone
I'm not alone
Can I see you for a moment?
I thought Seoha would ask to see him first.
I didn't know
So quickly
I have something to tell you.
I respected you, team leader.
The team leader
You're so cool
It's not too much for me.
But
What I like is something else.
my heart
It's someone else
person you like
There is
It's like a final goodbye.
All you have to do is do a good job
I want to do well too
A pretty good new guy came in.
Yes, that's right
Oh, I sent it on Friday.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm in the process of editing it now.
Yes yes
sorry
Ah
It's okay
Let's go
What happened
doa cell phone
why did you do that
brother
This isn't your cell phone.
I would have told you not to touch it.
If you don't like it
what you like
Doa no
what do you know
Hey
If you don't want to be hit, don't stand out.
Who do you like?
As long as the other person is not hurt
It's the heart
who confessed
How do I feel?
a little scared
anyone
I'm afraid of getting hurt
That's me
Whether it's someone else
That's my number one fear
Let's end it like this
yes
Don't start
I did
It started off wrong
The ending is not wrong either.
You can start again
Don't hurt yourself
Let’s protect it first.
Because that's the number of topics
Your master
They won't accept it.
I am Mr. Haram’s flower.
former member
I won't give up
Harama
brother
Just for a moment
It's okay
I have my brother's cell phone
I hid it on purpose
Now there's nothing to make you uncomfortable
I'm sorry
For telling me the truth
thank you
now
That's enough
Go in
They told me to wear clothes and go around
I don't like it
Ah, something like this
before my eyes
They say don’t go around buried.
I want to be kissed
Oh really
Hahaha hahaha ah
Come out quickly
3 years ago
It's the darkest time of my life
I thought of him
It came like a lie
It was first love
a little bigger than me
Without any effort
friendly
my boyfriend
Put all the complicated things aside for a moment
I only think about my body and the person in front of me.
But you know what
Ju Ji Soo
Must have a partner
It's a sport you can do